<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<feature
      id="net.sf.commonclipse"
      label="net.sf.commonclipse"
      version="1.0.1"
      provider-name="Fabrizio Giustina"
      os="aix,hpux,linux,macosx,qnx,solaris,win32"
      ws="carbon,gtk,motif,photon,win32"
      nl="en_US"
      arch="PA_RISC,ppc,sparc,x86">

   <description url="http://commonclipse.sourceforge.net/">
      Commonclipse is an eclipse plugin for jakarta commons-lang users.
It features automatic generation of the following methods using commons-lang builders: toString(), hashcode(), equals(Object), compareTo(Object).
   </description>

   <copyright>
      (c) 2003, 2004 Fabrizio Giustina
   </copyright>

   <license>
      /* ====================================================================
 * The Apache Software License, Version 1.1
 *
 * Copyright (c) 2000 The Apache Software Foundation.  All rights
 * reserved.
 *
 * Redistribution and use in source and binary forms, with or without
 * modification, are permitted provided that the following conditions
 * are met:
 *
 * 1. Redistributions of source code must retain the above copyright
 *    notice, this list of conditions and the following disclaimer.
 *
 * 2. Redistributions in binary form must reproduce the above copyright
 *    notice, this list of conditions and the following disclaimer in
 *    the documentation and/or other materials provided with the
 *    distribution.
 *
 * 3. The end-user documentation included with the redistribution,
 *    if any, must include the following acknowledgment:
 *       &quot;This product includes software developed by the
 *        Apache Software Foundation (http://www.apache.org ).&quot;
 *    Alternately, this acknowledgment may appear in the software itself,
 *    if and wherever such third-party acknowledgments normally appear.
 *
 * 4. The names &quot;Apache&quot; and &quot;Apache Software Foundation&quot; must
 *    not be used to endorse or promote products derived from this
 *    software without prior written permission. For written
 *    permission, please contact apache@apache.org.
 *
 * 5. Products derived from this software may not be called &quot;Apache&quot;,
 *    nor may &quot;Apache&quot; appear in their name, without prior written
 *    permission of the Apache Software Foundation.
 *
 * THIS SOFTWARE IS PROVIDED ``AS IS&apos;&apos; AND ANY EXPRESSED OR IMPLIED
 * WARRANTIES, INCLUDING, BUT NOT LIMITED TO, THE IMPLIED WARRANTIES
 * OF MERCHANTABILITY AND FITNESS FOR A PARTICULAR PURPOSE ARE
 * DISCLAIMED.  IN NO EVENT SHALL THE APACHE SOFTWARE FOUNDATION OR
 * ITS CONTRIBUTORS BE LIABLE FOR ANY DIRECT, INDIRECT, INCIDENTAL,
 * SPECIAL, EXEMPLARY, OR CONSEQUENTIAL DAMAGES (INCLUDING, BUT NOT
 * LIMITED TO, PROCUREMENT OF SUBSTITUTE GOODS OR SERVICES; LOSS OF
 * USE, DATA, OR PROFITS; OR BUSINESS INTERRUPTION) HOWEVER CAUSED AND
 * ON ANY THEORY OF LIABILITY, WHETHER IN CONTRACT, STRICT LIABILITY,
 * OR TORT (INCLUDING NEGLIGENCE OR OTHERWISE) ARISING IN ANY WAY OUT
 * OF THE USE OF THIS SOFTWARE, EVEN IF ADVISED OF THE POSSIBILITY OF
 * SUCH DAMAGE.
 * ====================================================================
 *
 * This software consists of voluntary contributions made by many
 * individuals on behalf of the Apache Software Foundation.  For more
 * information on the Apache Software Foundation, please see
 * &lt;http://www.apache.org &gt;.
 *
 * Portions of this software are based upon public domain software
 * originally written at the National Center for Supercomputing Applications,
 * University of Illinois, Urbana-Champaign.
 */
   </license>

   <url>
      <update label="Commonclipse update site" url="http://commonclipse.sourceforge.net"/>
      <discovery label="Commonclipse web site" url="http://commonclipse.sourceforge.net" type="web"/>
   </url>

   <requires>
      <import plugin="org.eclipse.core.resources"/>
      <import plugin="org.eclipse.ui"/>
      <import plugin="org.eclipse.jdt.core"/>
      <import plugin="org.eclipse.jdt.ui"/>
      <import plugin="org.eclipse.ui.workbench.texteditor"/>
      <import plugin="org.eclipse.jface.text"/>
   </requires>

   <plugin
         id="net.sf.commonclipse"
         download-size="37926"
         install-size="37926"
         version="1.0.1"/>

</feature>
