<?xml version="1.0"?>
<document>
    <properties>
        <title>Commonclipse configuration</title>
        <author email="fgiust(at)sourceforge.net">Fabrizio Giustina</author>
    </properties>

    <body>
        <section name="Configuration">
            <p>
                Commonclipse lets you configure different aspects in generateed methods. After installing the plugin you
                will find a new "Commonclipse" Preference page in "Window"->"Preferences" menu under the "Java" section.
            </p>

            <subsection name="ToString">
                <p>toString type:</p>
                <ul>
                    <li>
                        <strong>Use javabean properties</strong>
                        : the toString() method will contains all the readable javabean properties in the current class
                        (defined by getXXX or isXXX methods). This is mostly useful for dataobjects you are writing to a
                        log or displaying in a jsp page with the help of jsp tags (maybe using
                        <a href="http://displaytag.sourceforge.net">the display tag library</a>
                        ?). The javabean is accessed using the getter method or using the field with the same name if
                        existing.
                    </li>
                    <li>
                        <strong>Use fields</strong>
                        : standard toString() with all the fields in the current class, plus public or protected fields
                        in superclasses.
                    </li>
                </ul>

                <p>
                    ToString style: you can left it blank to use the default implementation, choose one of the available
                    jakarta implementations (ToStringStyle.DEFAULT_STYLE, ToStringStyle.MULTI_LINE_STYLE,
                    ToStringStyle.NO_FIELD_NAMES_STYLE, ToStringStyle.SIMPLE_STYLE) or provide your own ToStringStyle.
                </p>

            </subsection>

            <subsection name="General">
                <p>
                    <strong>Append super in XXX</strong>
                    : all the jakarta builders support an "appendSuper()" method to add the superclass implementation to
                    the current method. You can choose to enable it for any of the supported method.
                </p>
                <p>
                    <strong>Declare method parameters as final</strong>
                    (from version 1.2) : Add "final" to parameters in compareTo and equals() methods.
                </p>
                <p>
                    <strong>add an instance equality check to equals()</strong>
                    (from version 1.1) : Add an optional check (
                    <code>if (this == compared) return true</code>
                    ) to equals. This will speed up comparison when evaluating equals between two pointers to the same
                    instance
                </p>
                <p>
                    <strong>Overwrite existing methods without confirmation</strong>
                    : If this option is not selected commonclipse will ask before deleting existing methods.
                </p>
            </subsection>

            <subsection name="Excluded fields">
                <p>
                    <strong>Fields/properties not included in generated methods</strong>
                    : You can add any property you don't want to be included in methods here. For example you can avoid
                    fields defining Loggers or the standard class javabean property (Object#getClass()) to appear in
                    generated toString(). From version 1.1 you can use ? and * wildcards in names.
                </p>
            </subsection>


        </section>

    </body>
</document>
